<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Game Analytics on Hazelsinki</title><link>https://gokarna-hugo.netlify.app/tags/game-analytics/</link><description>Recent content in Game Analytics on Hazelsinki</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2025 17:55:28 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gokarna-hugo.netlify.app/tags/game-analytics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Falling Love in Nostalgia with Monopoly Go</title><link>https://gokarna-hugo.netlify.app/posts/monoploy_go/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2025 17:55:28 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://gokarna-hugo.netlify.app/posts/monoploy_go/</guid><description>&lt;p>Monopoly Go has become a big hit since it has launched in 2023. As someone who works in mobile game analytics, I find it really cool how the game balances engagement mechanics with monetization.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>It definitely brings good memories to many people from childhood where they casually bankrupting friends or make them pay higher rents for the cool properties they build. Honestly for me it was about all of the above and also good laughter.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Game Analytics 101</title><link>https://gokarna-hugo.netlify.app/posts/game_analytics101/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 17:55:28 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://gokarna-hugo.netlify.app/posts/game_analytics101/</guid><description>&lt;p>There are many tools available now that can help the teams to make products ready faster than ever. Although the key metrics teams need to focus are still the same. AI can help us generate content, personalize experiences, and even predict user behavior. But if teams don’t follow the &lt;strong>key metrics&lt;/strong> — DAU, retention, ARPU, session lengths, conversion funnels — it is basically flying blind.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Knowing what’s happening in the game — and more importantly, &lt;em>why&lt;/em> — will always be relevant.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Analysts Collaborating with QA</title><link>https://gokarna-hugo.netlify.app/posts/analyts_qa/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 17:55:28 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://gokarna-hugo.netlify.app/posts/analyts_qa/</guid><description>&lt;p>Data analysts are always getting questions — about the performance of new events, the health of the game, or how a new feature is doing.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>But what is really important &lt;strong>before&lt;/strong> diving into those questions?&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="how-you-can-implement-some-processes-in-the-team">How you can implement some processes in the team?&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>It is always good to emphasis the importance of communication in the team and with every craft. As data analyst embedded in game teams I prefer to discuss many things earlier with the feature owners, developers and QA. Here is how I plan things:&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>