<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Projects on Hazelsinki</title><link>hazelsinki.me/projects/</link><description>Recent content in Projects on Hazelsinki</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="hazelsinki.me/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Blüdhaven</title><link>hazelsinki.me/projects/bludhaven/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>hazelsinki.me/projects/bludhaven/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="history">History&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Blüdhaven was a former whaling town, which was officially incorporated as a &amp;ldquo;Commonwealth&amp;rdquo; in 1912. The town had a generally poor socio-economic populace, owing in part to failed efforts to transform itself into a manufacturing and shipping center.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Building a Shiny App to Visualise My Last.fm Data</title><link>hazelsinki.me/projects/shiny_post/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>hazelsinki.me/projects/shiny_post/</guid><description>&lt;p>As a long-time &lt;strong>Last.fm&lt;/strong> user (about 15 years) and a data nerd, I’ve always been curious about my listening patterns. I used to look at my data by downloading a CSV and creating some chart via &lt;strong>tidyverse&lt;/strong> functions. This time I decided to build a Shiny App that visualizes my Last.fm streaming history — and it turned out to be both fun and insightful!&lt;/p>
 &lt;div style="flex: 1; min-width: 250px;">
 &lt;img src="hazelsinki.me/images/shiny1.jpg" alt="Dancing" style="width: 100%; border-radius: 10px;">
 &lt;/div>
&lt;h2 id="what-the-app-does">What the App Does&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>My app provides an interactive dashboard that helps me explore my music habits over time. Here’s what it includes:&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>R-Ladies Helsinki</title><link>hazelsinki.me/projects/r_ladies_helsinki/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>hazelsinki.me/projects/r_ladies_helsinki/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="organisation">Organisation&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://rladies.org">R-Ladies&lt;/a> is a great organisation where people come together, learn and collaborate with each other while being in a safe space.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>You can read the mission of the organisation &lt;a href="https://rladies.org/about-us/mission/">here&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="helsinki-chapter">Helsinki Chapter&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>I was the organiser of R-Ladies Istanbul for about 3 years. After I moved to Helsinki I met the lovely organisers of Helsinki chapter and after sometime I took over the chapter. I am very happy to part of this organisation and spread the love and joy of creating things together.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>