<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Hazelsinki</title><link>https://superlative-snickerdoodle-13f9c6.netlify.app/</link><description>Recent content on Hazelsinki</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2025 17:55:28 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://superlative-snickerdoodle-13f9c6.netlify.app/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Falling Love in Nostalgia with Monopoly Go</title><link>https://superlative-snickerdoodle-13f9c6.netlify.app/posts/monoploy_go/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2025 17:55:28 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://superlative-snickerdoodle-13f9c6.netlify.app/posts/monoploy_go/</guid><description>&lt;p>Monopoly Go has become a big hit since it has launched in 2023. As someone who works in mobile game analytics, I find it really cool how the game balances engagement mechanics with monetization.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>It definitely brings good memories to many people from childhood where they casually bankrupting friends or make them pay higher rents for the cool properties they build. Honestly for me it was about all of the above and also good laughter.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Game Analytics 101</title><link>https://superlative-snickerdoodle-13f9c6.netlify.app/posts/game_analytics101/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 17:55:28 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://superlative-snickerdoodle-13f9c6.netlify.app/posts/game_analytics101/</guid><description>&lt;p>There are many tools available now that can help the teams to make products ready faster than ever. Although the key metrics teams need to focus are still the same. AI can help us generate content, personalize experiences, and even predict user behavior. But if teams don’t follow the &lt;strong>key metrics&lt;/strong> — DAU, retention, ARPU, session lengths, conversion funnels — it is basically flying blind.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Knowing what’s happening in the game — and more importantly, &lt;em>why&lt;/em> — will always be relevant.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Analysts Collaborating with QA</title><link>https://superlative-snickerdoodle-13f9c6.netlify.app/posts/analyts_qa/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 17:55:28 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://superlative-snickerdoodle-13f9c6.netlify.app/posts/analyts_qa/</guid><description>&lt;p>Data analysts are always getting questions — about the performance of new events, the health of the game, or how a new feature is doing.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>But what is really important &lt;strong>before&lt;/strong> diving into those questions?&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="how-you-can-implement-some-processes-in-the-team">How you can implement some processes in the team?&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>It is always good to emphasis the importance of communication in the team and with every craft. As data analyst embedded in game teams I prefer to discuss many things earlier with the feature owners, developers and QA. Here is how I plan things:&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>About Me</title><link>https://superlative-snickerdoodle-13f9c6.netlify.app/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://superlative-snickerdoodle-13f9c6.netlify.app/about/</guid><description>&lt;p>Hey there! 👋 I&amp;rsquo;m &lt;strong>Hazel&lt;/strong> — a data analyst by day, swing dancer by night 💃&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I am originally from Istanbul and I’ve been living in Helsinki for more than 6 years now. I absolutely love it here! 🇫🇮 I&amp;rsquo;m fluent in Finnish at a B1 level (I even passed the YKI test!). It’s been a rewarding journey embracing both the culture and the language.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I’ve spent over 8 years in the gaming industry, working with studios like Seriously, Rovio, and Supercell — helping out on projects that made games a bit more fun and players a bit more hooked.I specialize in:&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Blüdhaven</title><link>https://superlative-snickerdoodle-13f9c6.netlify.app/projects/bludhaven/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://superlative-snickerdoodle-13f9c6.netlify.app/projects/bludhaven/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="history">History&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Blüdhaven was a former whaling town, which was officially incorporated as a &amp;ldquo;Commonwealth&amp;rdquo; in 1912. The town had a generally poor socio-economic populace, owing in part to failed efforts to transform itself into a manufacturing and shipping center.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Building a Shiny App to Visualise My Last.fm Data</title><link>https://superlative-snickerdoodle-13f9c6.netlify.app/projects/shiny_post/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://superlative-snickerdoodle-13f9c6.netlify.app/projects/shiny_post/</guid><description>&lt;p>As a long-time &lt;strong>Last.fm&lt;/strong> user (about 15 years) and a data nerd, I’ve always been curious about my listening patterns. I used to look at my data by downloading a CSV and creating some chart via &lt;strong>tidyverse&lt;/strong> functions. This time I decided to build a Shiny App that visualizes my Last.fm streaming history — and it turned out to be both fun and insightful!&lt;/p>
 &lt;div style="flex: 1; min-width: 250px;">
 &lt;img src="https://superlative-snickerdoodle-13f9c6.netlify.app/images/shiny1.jpg" alt="Dancing" style="width: 100%; border-radius: 10px;">
 &lt;/div>
&lt;h2 id="what-the-app-does">What the App Does&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>My app provides an interactive dashboard that helps me explore my music habits over time. Here’s what it includes:&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>R-Ladies Helsinki</title><link>https://superlative-snickerdoodle-13f9c6.netlify.app/projects/r_ladies_helsinki/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://superlative-snickerdoodle-13f9c6.netlify.app/projects/r_ladies_helsinki/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="organisation">Organisation&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://rladies.org">R-Ladies&lt;/a> is a great organisation where people come together, learn and collaborate with each other while being in a safe space.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>You can read the mission of the organisation &lt;a href="https://rladies.org/about-us/mission/">here&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="helsinki-chapter">Helsinki Chapter&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>I was the organiser of R-Ladies Istanbul for about 3 years. After I moved to Helsinki I met the lovely organisers of Helsinki chapter and after sometime I took over the chapter. I am very happy to part of this organisation and spread the love and joy of creating things together.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>